http://www.caslt.org/en/privacy-policy

Menu
General Information
The Association
About CASLTCASLT’s 50th AnniversaryBoard of DirectorsNational CouncilStaffAnnual General MeetingAnnual ReportsCASLT Community
PartnersMedia
RéflexionsCASLT’s NewsletterNews ReleasesMember Services
Membership
Become a MemberRenew Your MembershipMember ServicesMembership CategoriesAwards and Grants
Robert Roy AwardHonorary Lifetime Member AwardH.H. Stern AwardResearch and Special Initiatives Grants for TeachersPromoting the Interests of Members
Networking Day and Annual General MeetingOther Meetings and RepresentationsCASLT MembershipsAffinity programsPedagogical Resources
Professional Information
About the CEFRThe Neurolinguistic ApproachResources
CASLT ResourcesOther ResourcesProfessional Development
Workshops/Professional Learning
CASLT Chez-Vous (CCV)Languages Without Borders (LWB)Past CASLT ConferencesOnline PD ActivitiesCalendar of PD ActivitiesPD Resources
CASLT PD ResourcesResearch and Survey Reports (Panorama)Other PD ResourcesCASLT Initiatives
CASLT Learning CentreAboriginal Languages GatheringWhy Learn Languages?
What the Research Shows
Comprehensive Reviews, Reports and PresentationsSpecific Areas of ImpactResources
Provincial and Territorial ResourcesNational ResourcesClassroom, School and Community ResourcesLanguages Build… Video Contest“Languages Build...” Advocacy ToolkitWhy Learn a Specific Language?
Choose your LanguageProjects
FSL Teacher Education Project The StudyEthicsConsortiumParticipate
Imprimer
Font-size
A-
A
A+
General Information
The Association
About CASLTCASLT’s 50th AnniversaryBoard of DirectorsNational CouncilStaffAnnual General MeetingAnnual Reports
CASLT Community
Partners
Media
RéflexionsGuidelines for WritersAdvertising GuidelinesCASLT’s NewsletterNews Releases
Member Services
Membership
Become a MemberRenew Your MembershipMember ServicesMembership CategoriesIndividual MemberInstitutional MemberStudent Member
Awards and Grants
Robert Roy AwardHonorary Lifetime Member AwardH.H. Stern AwardResearch and Special Initiatives Grants for Teachers
Promoting the Interests of Members
Networking Day and Annual General MeetingOther Meetings and RepresentationsCASLT MembershipsAffinity programs
Pedagogical Resources
Professional Information
About the CEFRThe Neurolinguistic Approach
Resources
CASLT ResourcesOther Resources
Professional Development
Workshops/Professional Learning
CASLT Chez-Vous (CCV)Languages Without Borders (LWB)Virtual Conference GuideRegistrationPresentersFeatured Presenters – Biographies and Abstracts of PresentationsConference SponsorsInformation for ExhibitorsConference ExhibitorsCall for ProposalsCultural PerformersPast CASLT ConferencesOnline PD ActivitiesCalendar of PD Activities
PD Resources
CASLT PD ResourcesResearch and Survey Reports (Panorama)Other PD Resources
CASLT Initiatives
CASLT Learning CentreAboriginal Languages Gathering
Why Learn Languages?
What the Research Shows
Comprehensive Reviews, Reports and PresentationsSpecific Areas of ImpactCognitive ImpactAcademic ImpactPersonal ImpactSocietal ImpactIntercultural CompetenciesEconomic ImpactStudents with ExceptionalitiesAdditional Language Learning
Resources
Provincial and Territorial ResourcesNational ResourcesClassroom, School and Community ResourcesLanguages Build… Video Contest“Languages Build...” Advocacy Toolkit
Why Learn a Specific Language?
Choose your LanguageAboriginal LanguagesAmerican Sign LanguageArabicChineseFrenchGermanGreekHindiItalianJapaneseKoreanPortuguesePunjabiRussianSpanish
Projects
FSL Teacher Education Project The StudyEthicsConsortiumParticipate
Home
»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
CASLT is committed to ensuring the accuracy, confidentiality, integrity, and security of all personal information. Our responsibility for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information provided by our members is an important tenet in our organization.
We use the term “personal” to describe information that identifies an individual, such as home address, home telephone number, credit card information, member identification number, or password. Publicly available information, such as information on a business card or on a LinkedIn profile (name, job title, business address, business telephone, and work email address), is not considered personal information.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
We often communicate with members regarding our activities, products, and services, as well as during membership recruitment campaigns. We collect and use personal information to provide the programs and services members have requested from us, or for the purposes set out in this policy.
Your own personal information is used to communicate with you about your membership in CASLT and the services that we provide. We may contact you to conduct surveys in our continual effort to improve our services.
We will only ask for information that we need and only when we need it. When we ask, we will explain why we need it and what we are going to do with it. We will seek your prior consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of the information as required by applicable privacy legislation.
Please note that by becoming a member of CASLT, you agree that we will collect, use, and disclose information about you. Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you may refuse to consent. You may also withdraw your consent to any further collection, use, or disclosure of information about you at any time. If our intended disclosures or uses of information change, we will notify you accordingly.
Information that does not identify individuals, collected through surveys, existing files, and public archives, may be used by CASLT to analyze its markets and to develop or enhance member services.
Disclosure
To enable us to provide the services that members have requested from us more efficiently, CASLT may share personal information with selected third parties acting on our behalf as our contractors, suppliers, or service providers. Such third-party service providers only receive such information as is necessary in the circumstances. Information provided to third parties may be used only for the purpose stipulated and is subject to strict terms of confidentiality.
Accuracy
We commit to ensuring that the information we hold about you is as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as possible. When your personal information changes, please make sure to update your member profile on CASLT’s website.
Security
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Security measures such as locked cabinets, restricted access, passwords, and encryption have been adopted to protect your personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized access, etc. Employees with access shall use your personal information only in strict accordance with the CASLT Privacy Policy and the laws applicable.
Questions or Concerns
We will be happy to respond to inquiries or complaints about CASLT’s handling of personal information. If you have questions about the collection, use, disclosure, or security of your personal information, or if you simply want to know whether we have any of your personal information on file, please contact our membership administrator at 1-877-727-0994 or This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Scroll to top
